fiat.co.uk 2017-08-14

# Privacy Policy | Fiat UK

**There have been changes in the law relating to Cookies, please see below our updated Cookie policy. You can also visit our dedicatedCookies page, which explains what a Cookie is, how they are used, and how they can be removed or rejected.  
**  
This website is operated by Fiat Chrysler Automobiles UK Ltd ("Fiat" or "Fiat Chrysler Automobiles UK"). For more information about us and how you can contact us please see the [Contact Us](http://www.fiat.co.uk/uk/header-contacts) section. The financial services available from the [Finance](http://www.fiat.co.uk/uk/financial-services) section of the Fiat website are provided by Fiat Financial Services, a trading style of FCA Automotive Services UK Ltd. The contract hire services available from the [Finance](http://www.fiat.co.uk/uk/financial-services) section of the Fiat website are provided by Fiat Contract Hire, a trading style of Leasys UK Ltd. 

FCA Italy SpA is the Italian parent company of the Fiat companies operating in the UK. FCA Italy SpA is a company within the Fiat Chrysler Automobiles N.V. group of companies and any references to the "Fiat Group" in this policy are references to Fiat Chrysler Automobiles N.V. and its subsidiary companies. 

Fiat is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. We have established this privacy policy to demonstrate the care with which we will treat your information.

####  **Privacy**

We will always respect your privacy and any personal information that you give us. We will always endeavour to comply with the Data Protection Act 1998 and any associated legal regulations concerning data protection.

When you visit this website, your personal data is only stored if submitted by you when requesting information or using any service available on the site, for example where you might request a test drive or register your details in the 'My Garage' section or request an insurance quote from Fiat Consumer Services.

####  **Use of your information**

This policy describes how we and other companies in the Fiat Group (collectively referred to as "we") intend to use your personal information. If this differs for any reason, such as in the case of data relating to children, we will make this clear at the time of data collection.

If you make a specific request for us to contact you, such as requesting a brochure or a myFiat card, we will use the personal information you provide to fulfil your enquiry. We may disclose your information to Fiat Appointed companies and agents for this purpose. Where you request a service provided independently by our franchised dealers or by other Fiat Appointed companies (for example, a test drive or a quote from Fiat Insurance), we may share your information with them to fulfil this request. At any page on this web site where you have the opportunity to submit your personal information, you will be given the opportunity to object to us, our franchised dealers and other Fiat Appointed Companies making further use of your data. You will also be given the opportunity to specify whether we, our franchised dealers and other Fiat Appointed Companies can communicate with you by e-mail, SMS and/or fax.

If you create a myFiat account and log a vehicle against that account you will be considered to be an owner or driver of that vehicle. As such, your details may be passed to one or more of Fiat's agents, partners or franchised dealers to enable them to update their vehicle records. These partners may contact you to tell you about services related to your vehicle such as extended warranties, Roadside Assistance cover or registration with the International Security Register. If you do not wish your details to be passed to any of Fiat's agents, partners or dealers you should clear the 'contact me by post' tick box on the myFiat registration page, or do so after registering, in the myAccount section of the myFiat portal. 

If you do not object to us making further use of your data we, our franchised dealers or other Fiat Appointed Companies may keep your data for a reasonable period and use the data given for our own internal research purposes or to contact you in the future to let you know about Fiat's other products and services (such as motor insurance or financial products) or special offers that might be of interest to you or to ask you what you think of us in order to improve our customer service. 

We will only contact you by e-mail, telephone or post if you have consented to our doing so. We may notify you on the relevant page of our website that by submitting your details to us, you are giving your consent to receiving marketing messages from us and from our franchised dealers. We will however, always give you the opportunity to object to receiving marketing messages. Your personal information may be passed to and processed by FCA Italy SpA or Fiat Group companies, Fiat's franchised dealers and other agents who act under our direction. We may also share your information with our franchised dealers for use in connection with their business as Fiat franchised dealers. You may hear separately from our franchised dealers about our ranges of Fiat vehicles or from our agents and representatives about related motoring products and services, such as motor insurance or financial products. 

Please note that certain benefits available under the myFiat Card scheme, managed via the myRewards section of the myFiat pages on this site, may require us to contact you by e-mail to facilitate the redemption of the benefit. If you opt out of receiving e-mails on your myFiat account we will not send you the relevant redemption e-mail with the result that you may be unable to redeem the benefit in question. 

Fiat will not pass your details to unrelated third party organisations except where we are legally obliged to do so (for example in relation to vehicle safety issues or financial regulation) or in order to prevent and detect fraud. 

To help us to make credit decisions about you, to prevent fraud, to check your identity and to prevent money laundering, we may search the files of credit reference agencies who will record any credit searches on your file. We may also disclose details of how you conduct your account to such agencies. The information will be used by other credit grantors for making credit decisions about you and the people with whom you are financially associated, for fraud prevention, money laundering prevention and occasionally for tracing debtors.

####  **Your consent**

By submitting your information to Fiat, you consent to the use of that information as set out in this policy. If we change our privacy policy we will post the changes on this page, and may place notices on other pages of the website, so that you may be aware of the information we collect and how we use it at all times. Continued use of the service will signify that you agree to any such changes. 

If you give us information about another person, you confirm that the other person has appointed you to act on his/her behalf and has agreed that you can give consent on his/her behalf to the processing of his/her personal data in accordance with this policy.

####  **Forward to a friend**

If you use the 'forward to a friend' facility, Fiat Chrysler Automobiles UK Ltd will pass your name and email address to the friend you are forwarding the information to. 

#### **Right to object**

You have the right to correct any inaccuracies in the personal data we hold about you, or to change your mind about the usage rights you have given us. Write to us at Fiat Chrysler Automobiles UK Ltd, 240 Bath Road, Slough, Berkshire, SL1 4DX United Kingdom. You also have the right to ask us for a copy of the information about you, which we hold on our systems. We may charge you a small fee for the provision of this information to cover administration costs.

####  **Updating your details**

If any of the information that you have provided to us changes, for example if you change your e-mail address, name or payment details or if you wish to cancel your registration, please let us know the correct details by sending an e-mail to [privacyuk@fcagroup.com](mailto:privacyuk@fcagroup.com) or by writing to us at Fiat Chrysler Automobiles UK Ltd, 240 Bath Road, Slough, Berkshire, SL1 4DX United Kingdom.

####  **Children**

We may occasionally create on-line games, which children may play. Parents should supervise their children's online activities and consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers that help provide a Child-friendly online environment. These tools can also prevent children from disclosing online their name, address, and other personal information without parental permission.

####  **Security**

Fiat strictly protects the security of your personal information and your choices for its intended use. We use current industry standard technology to maintain the confidentiality and accuracy of the information you provide to us. To protect your personal information, we use "secure servers" with industry standard SSL 128 bit key encryption. However, the internet is not a secure medium so we cannot guarantee that any information you submit to us will be free from unauthorised third party intrusion.

####  **Cookies Policy**

A cookie is a small amount of data, often including a unique identifier that is sent to your computer or mobile phone browser from a website and is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Websites can send cookies to your browser if your preferences allow it, but to protect your privacy, a website can only access cookies that it has already sent to you. Many websites do this whenever a user visits, in order to track levels of online traffic. 

On the fiat.co.uk website, cookies record your preferences to allow us to tailor the website to your needs. Users can set their devices to accept all cookies, to notify them when a cookie is received, or to not receive any cookies at all. The latter means that some features cannot be provided you may not be able to enjoy the full website experience. 

When you visit a Fiat Chrysler Automobiles UK website, the pages you see are downloaded to your device along with a cookie. Many websites do this to understand whether the device (and therefore probably its user) has visited the website before. This is done by checking to see it can find the cookie left there on the previous visit.   
Each internet browser works differently, so check the "Help" menu to find out how to change your cookie preferences. 

Information gathered by cookies helps us to analyse our website visitors and provide you with a better user experience.   
In addition, Fiat uses an independent research company, Psyma. They gather user feedback via an online survey including cookies, which is embedded on our website. We use this type of information to help improve the services we provide to our users. 

In some areas of the Fiat.co.uk website we may embed photos and video content from websites such as YouTube and Flickr. Therefore when you visit a page with content embedded, you may be presented with cookies from these websites. Fiat Chrysler Automobiles UK does not control the distribution of these cookies. You will need to check the relevant third party website for more information. 

A list of the main cookies that Fiat Chrysler Automobiles UK websites set (and what each is used for) together with ways to minimise the number of cookies you receive, can be found in the Cookies section.

####  **Monitoring**

To make sure we follow your instructions correctly and to improve our service to you through training of our staff, we may monitor or record telephone calls between us. 

Last updated: [8 April 2015].
